allthetopbananas.com 2010-01-02

# All the Top Bananas - The UK's most helpful job search engine

And here is the legal privacy stuff...

**PROTECTION NOTICE & COOKIE POLICY**

The Company is committed to protecting your privacy. The Company knows that you care how information about you is used and appreciates your trust in it to do that carefully and sensibly. At times you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself (name, email address, postcode etc.). By entering your details in the fields as requested you enable the Company to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, the Company will treat that information in accordance with this notice and policy. All service related email correspondence includes instructions on how to ‘unsubscribe’ from the service to which you have subscribed. Our services are designed to give you the information that you want to receive not to bombard you with information you do not want. The Company will act in accordance with current legislation. 

**Use of Data.**

The Company will use your personal details and information it obtains from other sources to provide you with its goods and services, for administration and customer services, for credit scoring, for marketing, to analyse your purchasing preferences and to ensure that the content, services and advertising that it offers are tailored to your needs and interests. The Company may keep your information for a reasonable period for these purposes. The Company may need to share your information with its service providers and partners. The Company may disclose personal data in order to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation. 

**What are Cookies?**

Cookies are small pieces of information that a Internet Site might store on your computer or access device. They allow Internet Sites to remember who you are. Typically your browser will store each cookie as a small text file. A cookie will always contain the domain name of the originating Internet Site. For security, only the originating Internet Site has permission to read the cookie. 

**Cookies are Used.**

When you log in to the Internet Site the Company will set a cookie containing a randomly generated unique reference number. This anonymous number allows the Company to identify you. The Company will never store your personal information directly as a cookie. If, as you log in, you tick the checkbox labelled "Remember me", a persistent cookie will be set. Persistent cookies are not deleted when you close your browser, and will allow the Internet Site to recognise you on your next visit. 

**does the Company use Cookies?**

Advanced features of the site use Cookies to provide information you requested and to reduce you having to key in repeated fields. Cookies allow the Company to see how the Internet Site is being used. This information forms the basis of future development work, and so enables the Company to continually improve its Internet Site to best suit its users. They also allow the Internet Site to remember you when you log-in saving you needing to login.

**Cookies.**

Cookies can be easily deleted or disabled at any time through your browser’s preference menus so please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. Further information on controlling cookies is available at http://www.aboutcookies.org. Please be aware that if you do choose to disable cookies this site may not operate as expected and you may not be able to access various features.

**IP Address.**

When you visit our site, we may also log your IP address, a unique identifier for your connection at a point in time.

The Company also includes web beacons (also known as clear GIFs or web bugs) in its emails to track the success of its marketing campaigns. This means that if you open an email from the Company it can see which pages of the Internet Site you visit. 

**Credit References.**

In assessing your application for credit, to prevent fraud, to check your identity and to prevent money laundering, the Company may search the files of credit reference agencies who will record any credit searches on your file. The Company may also disclose details of how you conduct your account to such agencies. The information will be used by other credit grantors for making credit decisions about you and the people with whom you are financially associated, for fraud prevention, money laundering prevention and occasionally for tracing debtors. Information used for these purposes will include publicly available information such as electoral roll, county court judgments, bankruptcy orders or repossessions.

The Company may also share your information with its business partners in the travel, property, automotive, financial services, leisure, entertainment, advertising, media, retail and mail order business for marketing purposes or it may send you information about other organisations’ goods and services. The Company or its business partners may contact you by mail, telephone, fax, e-mail or other electronic messaging service with offers of goods and services or information that may be of interest to you e.g. holidays, cars, property, financial and leisure services, entertainment, media products, advertising, clothing or household goods. By providing the Company with your fax number, land line and/or mobile telephone numbers or email address you consent to being contacted by these methods for these purposes. If you do not wish to receive marketing information from the Company or from the Company’s business partners tick the appropriate box on the form you complete. 

**Personal Data out of the UK.**

By providing the Company with your personal information you also consent to the Company transferring your information to countries or jurisdictions which do not provide the same level of data protection as the UK, if necessary for the above purposes.

**Party Data.**

If you provide the Company with information about another person, you confirm that they have appointed you to act for them, to consent to the processing of their personal data including sensitive personal data and that you have informed them of the Company’s identity and the purposes (as set out above) for which their personal data will be processed.
